A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Campaigns, Series 5 FA440
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Campaigns, Series 5
1956-1970
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich) (1908-1979)
FA440
98.04 Cubic Feet 216 containers including but not limited to: 45 letter document boxes, 167 legal document boxes.
95.59 Cubic Feet 45 letter document boxes, 167 legal document boxes.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Scope and Contents
This series contains correspondence, background information, delegate and voting data, and some finance records for Nelson A. Rockefeller's gubernatorial and presidential campaigns from 1958 to 1970. There is also information from the campaign to reelect President Dwight D. Eisenhower in 1956 from supporters in New York.
Arrangement
The first subseries is the 1956 Eisenhower presidential reelection material. The following four subseries are the campaign materials for Nelson Rockefeller's successful runs for New York Governor. The next three subseries are campaig materials for Nelson Rockefeller's unsuccessful efforts to secure the Republican presidential nominiation. The final subseries is photographs from the various campaigns.
Presidential campaigns -- United States; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1958; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1962; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1966; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1970
- Campaigns, 1956-1970; 5; 98.04 Cubic Feet 216 containers including but not limited to: 45 letter document boxes, 167 legal document boxes.
  Arrangement
  Series 5 (Campaigns) is arranged in the following subseries:
  Subseries 1: New York State Citizens for Eisenhower, 1956 U.S. Presidential Campaign.
  Subseries 2: Citizens for Rockefeller-Keating, 1958 New York Gubernatorial Campaign.
  Subseries 3: Citizens for Rockefeller-Javitz, 1962 New York Gubernatorial Campaign.
  Subseries 4: 1966 New York Gubernatorial Campaign.
  Subseries 5: 1970 New York Gubernatorial Campaign.
  Subseries 6: 1960 U.S. Presidential Campaign.
  Subseries 7: 1964 U.S. Presidential Campaign.
  Subseries 8: 1968 U.S. Presidential Campaign.
  Subseries 9: Photographs for Campaigns.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contians correspondence, background information, delegate and voting data, and some finance records for Nelson A. Rockefeller's gubernatorial and presidential campaigns from 1958 to 1970. It also contains one series of materials on the reelection campaign of Presidnet Dwight D. Eisenhower from supporters in New York.
  - New York State Citizens for Eisenhower, 1956 U.S. Presidential Campaign, 1
    - Statements and Receipted Bills, 1956 May-June (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Statements and Receipted Bills, 1956 June-July (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Statements and Receipted Bills, 1956 July (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Campaign Bulletins, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Organizing Manual, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Campaign Materials, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Correspondence, committee formation certificates, new clippings, campaign manual, volunteer lists, committee lists.
    - Finances, Correspondence, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Bills and Statements, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Bills, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Bills, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Bills, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Bills, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Bills, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Bills, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Budget and Correspondence, 1956 April-June (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Budget and Correspondence, 1956 July-August (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Budget and Correspondence, 1956 September (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Budget and Correspondence, 1956 October (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Budget and Correspondence, 1956 November- 1957 June (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Executive Meetings Minutes, 1956 June 18-August 6 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Syracuse Meeting, Press Releases, 1956 September 29 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Memos, 1956 May 22-July 5 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Memos to Robert Mackall, 1956 July-October (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Fernando T. Amis Memos, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Memos, Booklet, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Organization Charts, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Youth Manual, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Openings, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      Harlem, Ike Center, 42nd Street, Mid-East; Miscellaneous; Brooklyn, Montague Street.
    - United Press Associations, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      Bills for photos, prices, correspondence.
    - Photos, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous Campaign Information, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 32)
      Volunteer instructions, small contributions memo, form letter to "Independent Citizen."
    - Advertising, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      Rate cards, newspaper, radio, TV, bus advertising.
    - Appointment of Woods McCahill as Chair for Albany County, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - "Register to Vote" Flyer, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Mail for Mackall; County Chairs List, Memos, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Wires to County Chairman, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Campaign Materials, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      National Citizens for Eisenhower Decorations Manual, registration flyer, apointment of Adrian Van Sinderen as Chairman of Kings County, miscellaneous publicity.
    - National Publicity, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      Press releases and Citizens for Eisenhower "Advance," 1956 Presidential Handbook.
    - Campaign Office Openings, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      Kings County, Queens County, Lexington Club, Edgecomb Club, Mid-Manhattan.
    - Openings; New York Ciry, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      Publicity plans, telegram lists, newspaper checklist, budget for New York grand opening.
    - Booklets, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      Drafts of proposed campaign booklet, memos, prices.
    - Press, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      Press clippings, Collier's (magazine), "Ike's Health" article.
    - Inter-Office Memos, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Speech Transcript, 1956 May 31 (Box 4, Folder 45)
      President Eisenhower at National Citizens for Eisenhower, New York City Statler Hotel.
    - Memos for Campaign Volunteers, Letter to Volunteers, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Projects Memos, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Radio Spots, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Press Releases, Appointments of County Chairs, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Press Releases, Appointments, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Volunteer and Registration Memos, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Alexander Halpern, Treasurer, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Alexander Halpern, Treasurer, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Appointment of County Chairman (A-M), 1956 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Appointment of County Chairman (N-W), 1956 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Mailing Lists, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Releases to be Written (Biographies), 1956 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Publicity, Mailings, Manuals, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Biographies for Appointments as County Chairs, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - News Clippings, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Bulk Mailing Permit, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Clipping Services, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - 1956 Speech Kit (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Biographies, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Clipping File on Thrasher, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Alexander Halpern Messages, 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Nassau County Final Report, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - "Advance" Newsletter, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 68)
      Issues, National Citizens for Eisenhower.
    - Advertising, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Applicant - Fernando T. Amis, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Campaign Manual, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Weekly Activity Reports, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - San Francisco Convention - Hotel Arrangements, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - McMahon Finance Receipts, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - House Organ - Press Releases, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - General Kilpatric Correspondence, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Financial Paperwork, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 77)
      Leases, typewriter rentals, insurance policies.
    - Campaign Literature, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Robert Marcus (Personal), 1956 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Photos and Candidate List, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Lloyd McMahon Miscellaneous Correspondendence, 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Office Materials, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 82)
      Sample letters sent to County Chairmen, organizing manual, campaign manual, band wagon organization, Republican platform.
    - Bronx County Correspondence, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - "Operation Fold Up", 1956 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Rally - Madison Square Garden, 1966 October 25 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Voter Registration, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Research, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Syracuse Meeting of County Chairmen, 1956 September 29 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Speakers Bureau, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Supplies, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Veterans Groups, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Volunteers; Weekly Activities Reports, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Radio - TV Publicity, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Press Release, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - National Citizens Press Releases, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Kings County, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Queens County, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Counties - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Counties - Albany - Correspondence and Reports, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Counties - Broome - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Counties - Alleghany - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Counties - Cattaraugus and Cayuga - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Counties - Chautauqua - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 103)
    - Counties - Chemung - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Counties - Chenango - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Counties - Clinton - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Counties - Columbia - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - Counties - Cortland - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Counties - Delaware - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 109)
    - Counties - Dutchess - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 110)
    - Counties - Erie - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Counties - Essex - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Counties - Franklin and Fulton - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 113)
    - Counties - Gennessee - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Counties - Greene, Hamilton and Herkimer - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Counties - Jefferson - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Counties - Lewis - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Counties - Livingston - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Counties - Madison - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Counties - Monroe - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Counties - Montgomery - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Counties - Nassau - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - Counties - Niagera - Correspondence and Press Clippings, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 123)
    - Counties - Oneida - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 124)
    - Counties - Onondaga - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 125)
    - Counties - Ontario - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 126)
    - Counties - Orange - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 127)
    - Counties - Orleans - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Counties - Oswego - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 129)
    - Counties - Otsego - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 130)
    - Counties - Putnam - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 131)
    - Counties - Rensselaer - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 132)
    - Counties - Richmond - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 133)
    - Counties - Rockland - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 134)
    - Counties - Saint Lawrence - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 135)
    - Counties - Saratoga - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 136)
    - Counties - Schenectady - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 137)
    - Counties - Schoharie - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 138)
    - Counties - Schuyler - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 139)
    - Counties - Seneca - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 140)
    - Counties - Steuben - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 141)
    - Counties - Suffolk - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 142)
    - Counties - Sullivan - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 143)
    - Counties - Tioga - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 144)
    - Counties - Tompkins - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 145)
    - Counties - Ulster - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 146)
    - Counties - Warren - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 147)
    - Counties - Washington and Wayne - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    - Counties - Westchester - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 149)
    - Counties - Wyoming - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 150)
    - Counties - Yates - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 151)
    - Salute to Eisenhower, 1956 January 21 (Box 10, Folder 152)
      Dinner at Madison Square Garden, correspondence, invitations, mailing lists.
    - Accounting, 1956 May 2-1957 January 3 (Box 10, Folder 153)
      Accounting reports, budget, bank statements.
    - Receipts, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 154)
      Bulk mailing receipts, trucking company receipts.
    - Miscellaneous Credits, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 155)
    - Petty Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 156 & 156A)
    - Check Registers, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 157)
    - Check Registers, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 158)
    - Petty Cash Book, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 159)
    - Correspondence; Campaign Wrap-up, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 160)
    - Receipts Journal, 1956 May 18-December (Box 11, Folder 161)
    - Treasurer's Report to Secretary of State, 1956 October 24-November 15 (Box 11, Folder 162)
    - Alexander Halpern Fundraising Correspondence File, 1952-1954 (Box 11, Folder 163)
  - Citizens for Rockefeller and Keating, 1958 New York Gubernatorial Campaign, 2
    - Reorganization - Change from Eisenhower Committee, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 164)
      Funds transfer.
    - Receipts Journal, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 165)
    - Disbursements Journal, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 166)
    - Finances, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 167)
    - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 168)
    - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 169)
    - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 170)
    - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 171)
    - Volume I - Discussion and Position Papers, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 172)
      Summary, economic, legal and social.
    - Volume I continued - Discussion and Position Papers, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 173)
      Summary, human welfare, population growth and financing, education, power and resources (no paper), governmental (no paper), and miscellaneous (no paper).
    - Position and Background Papers, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 174)
      Table of Contents, economic trends and business.
    - Position and Background Papers, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 175)
      Agriculture.
    - Position and Background Papers, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 176)
      Taxation and fiscal affairs, social insurance in New York.
    - Position and Background Papers, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 177)
      Labor management in New York State, crime.
    - Position and Background Papers, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 178)
      Juvenile delinquency, public welfare.
    - Position and Background Papers, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 179)
      Child welfare, health.
    - Position and Background Papers, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 180)
      Rehabilitation, education.
    - Position and Background Papers, 1958 June 20 (Box 13, Folder 181)
      Transportation.
    - Position and Background Papers, 1958 July 15 (Box 13, Folder 182)
    - Position and Background Papers, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 183)
      Special transportation problems of New York City, Metropolitan area.
    - Position and Background Papers, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 184)
      Policy concepts in housing (prepared for Rockefeller Brothers Fund, Inc.).
    - Labor Racketeering Memo by H.E.S., 1958 June 14 (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - New York Republican State Committee "Republican Advance" Newsletter, 1956-1958 (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Campaign Material, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 187)
      Organization manual, campaign literature, instructions to workers.
    - Letters to "Special Groups" (Clergy, Lawyers, etc.), 1958 (Box 14, Folder 188)
    - General List of Donors I, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 189)
    - General List of Donors II, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 190)
    - Forms - Stationery, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 191)
    - Women's Campaign Kit, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 192)
    - Real Estate - Rental Offices, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 193)
    - Campaign Literature, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 194)
    - Mailing and Printing Information, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 195)
    - "Campaign Express", 1958 (Box 15, Folder 196)
      Bills, correspondence, release and schedule. Photograph.
    - Section Leader Lists, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 197)
    - "Clubs" (Storefronts), 1958 (Box 15, Folder 198)
    - Inter-Office Mail Lists, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - "Standard Operating Procedure", 1958 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Democrats for Rockefeller, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 201)
      Brochure, correspondents, donor lists.
    - Volunteer Application Cards, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 202)
    - Mailings - Veterans, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 203)
      Optomotrists, doctors and special groups.
    - Fiesta; Rally, 1958 October (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Public Relations, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 205)
      Correspondence, proposals and memos.
    - Speaker Engagements; Speaker's Bureau, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 206)
    - Speech Materials, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 207)
      Speaker's data sheets, form letters seeking speakers.
    - Photos, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 208)
    - Bronx, Brooklyn and Staten Island Counties Organizational Material, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 209)
    - Westchester, Rockland and Suffolk Counties Ortanizational Material, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 210)
    - Erie County Organizational Material, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 211)
      Area 1 County
    - Nassau County Organizational Material, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 212)
    - Area 1 Counties Organizational Material, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 213)
      Niagara, Clantauqua, Cattaraugus, Orleans, Gennessea, Wyoming and Alleghaney.
    - Area 2 Counties Organizational Material, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 214)
      Monroe, Livingston, Ontario, Seneca, Wayne and Cayuga.
    - Area 3 Counties Organizational Material, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 215)
      Jefferson, Oswego, Onondaga and Lewis.
    - Area 4A Counties Organizational Material, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 216)
      Steuben, Schuyler, Chemung, Yates and Tompkins.
  - Citizens for Rockefeller and Javits, 1962 New York Gubernatorial Campaign, 3
    - Area 4B Counties Organizational Material, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 217)
      Broome, Cortland, Chenango, Tioga and Delaware.
    - Area 5 Counties Organizational Material, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 218)
      Oneida, Herkimer, Otsego and Madison.
    - Area 6 Counties Organizational Material, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 219)
      Albany, Schoharie, Rensselear, Schenectady, Washington, Essex, Hamilton (no papers), Warren, Saratoga, Fulton and Montgomery.
    - Area 7 Counties Organizational Material, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 220)
      Sullivan, Greene, Ulster, Columbia, Dutchess, Putnam and Orange.
    - Area 8 Counties Organizational Material, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 221)
      Saint Lawrence, Franklin and Clinton.
    - Campaign Memorabilia, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 222)
    - Speaker's Bureau - Correspondence, Groups, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 223)
    - Speaker's Bureau - Engagements - Cancelled, Postponed, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 224)
    - Speaker's Bureau - Reports, Correspondence, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 225)
    - Speaker's Bureau - "Engagements Referred to Republican State Committee", 1962 (Box 17, Folder 226)
    - Speaker Bureau - Biographies, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 227)
    - Cocktail Party Lists, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 228)
    - Vendors - Sound, Printed Material, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 229)
    - Volunteers, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 230)
      Requests to volunteer and replies, requests for "leterature."
    - Requests to Volunteer, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 231)
    - Volunteers, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 232)
    - External Correspondence, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 233)
    - Special Goups - Mailing, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 234)
    - Legal - Print Advertising, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 235)
    - Campaign Organization, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 236)
      Bios of leaders, preliminary budget, memo (May 28, 1962) to Halpern from Katz re: specific functions for campaign.
    - Young Republican Rally Kit, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 237)
    - Progress Report, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 238)
    - Campaign Novelties, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 239)
      Comic Book: "You Need Rockefeller and Javits," sheet music: "Vamos, Sigamos Todes a Rockefeller."
    - Speakers Bureau - Correspondence, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 240)
    - Javits Speaker's Kit; Fact Sheets, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 241)
      "The Javits Record, His Record and Views."
    - Republican Campaign Speaker's Kit, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 242)
    - Upstate Organization, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 243)
      Upstate Chairman, volunteers, lists and mailing labels for organizations, civic associatfions, churches, etc.
    - Sound Track Speakers and Script, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 244)
    - Spanish and Puerto Rican Groups, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 245)
    - Organizations in New York City, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 246)
    - Czechoslovak Program, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 247)
    - Spanish Speakers; Mobile Trailer, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 248)
    - Spanish Fiesta, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 249)
    - Internal Correspondence, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 250)
    - Chairmen, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 251)
    - Organization Charts, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 252)
    - Draft Letters, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 253)
    - Interfiling, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 254)
    - Interfiling, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 255)
    - Interfiling, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 256)
    - Interfiling, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 257)
    - Interfiling, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 258)
    - Reports and Correspondence, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 259)
      Labeled, "To be filed in proper county folder at start of 1964 Campaign."
    - Reports, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 260)
    - NAR Thank-you Notes (A-C), 1962 (Box 19, Folder 261)
    - NAR Thank-you Notes (B-D), 1962 (Box 19, Folder 262)
    - NAR Thank-you Notes (F-K), 1962 (Box 19, Folder 263)
    - NAR Thank-you Notes (H-K), 1962 (Box 20, Folder 264)
    - NAR Thank-you Notes (J-L), 1962 (Box 20, Folder 265)
    - NAR Thank-you Notes (M-P), 1962 (Box 20, Folder 266)
    - NAR Thank-you Notes (T-W), 1962 (Box 20, Folder 267 & 267a)
  - 1966 New York Gubernatorial Campaign, 4
    - Advertizing Agencies' Proposals, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 268)
    - Dean Alfanqe, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 269)
      Correspondence and reports of his campaign work.
    - Heritage Foundation Ads, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 270)
    - Appointments, Bronx and Richmond Counties, 1959-1965 (Box 21, Folder 271)
    - Miscellaneous Campaign Information, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 272)
      Area deputy campaign managers, expenses, correspondence, reports.